Finding Aid for the Mary Anne Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Personal Records, 1 VHS tape—Star Wars 1 Audio-cassette tape – I. 5 year Defense Plan II. The Organizations III. Building Security IV. Sources of Hope 3 audio-cassette tapes – Ed Hamlett interviews Mary Anne Smith, Dec. 26, 2001 2 Chinese Mao-style hats 1 Oversize Mother Jones Calendar 1972 1 Over
  - Day Planners—1984 and 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Address Book and Memo Book (Box 17, Folder 4)